Subtitles & Sync By lupiniam原创字幕 有错概不负责
Subtitles & Sync By FridayToker
拜拜, L.A.!
Bye, L.A.!
我们上!
Here we go.
我的朋友都是白痴
My friends are morons.
你最好小心点,免得被关进伦敦塔
You better be careful, you might end up in the Tower of London.
犯罪的话
Criminal.
可是它会是你的
But it's gonna be you.
- 忘了那架飞机吧 - 附带一提,你们真是无聊
- Forget THE plane. - This is backwards, by the way.
在这里 我们的面前, 正是美丽的...
And here in front of us, we have the beautiful...
多瑙河
Danube River.
我们在布拉格
We're doing Prague.
嗨, 保罗! 我们在伦敦塔了!
Hi, Paul! We're at the Tower of London!
接下来我们就要去基辅 我们要来找你了,保罗.
Here we come, Kiev. We're coming to see you, Paul.
你们真有够夸张
You guys are ridiculous.
-兄弟 这才好玩啊 -是阿,我能想像
- Dude, it was so much fun, man. - Yeah, I can imagine.
嘿,小姐们!你们想把东西放下了吗?
Hey, ladies! You wanna put your stuff away?
- 当然 - 你怎么弄到这的, 保罗
- Sure. - Some place you got here, Paul.
我赖着不走啊
I'm never leaving.
超棒的地方 对吧,克里斯?
Best place ever. Ain't it right, Chris?
- 我来拿吧,没关系的 - 我来 我来 让我来吧
- I got it, it's fine. - I'll take it. I got it. I insist.
我们睡哪呢?
Where are we sleeping?
别担心, 我会放一个枕头在阳台上的
I told you, I put a pillow on the patio for you.
"别担心, 我会放一个枕头在阳台上的"
"I told you, I put a pillow on the patio for you."
你当然睡我房间! 不然你以为你还能睡哪?
You're sleeping in my room! Where do you think you're sleeping?
喔 太好了 而且更棒的是 说不定房里还藏了几个小妞?
Oh, great. Even better. Some chick still sleeping in there?
可能有喔
Quite possibly.
我希望你有清理过床单 或是该烧掉它们
I hope you cleaned those sheets. Or burned them.
我听得到!
I heard that!
- 所以...基辅 哈? - 基辅, 宝贝!
- So, Kiev, huh? - Kiev, baby!
我原打算找到你地址的时候 踹你一脚的
I thought for sure your ADD would have kicked in by now.
兄弟 我告诉你 我都不想走了
Dude, I'm telling you, man. I don't think I'm leaving.
我爱死这里了! 那些小妞真他妈的吓死人
I love it here! The chicks, they're fuckin' amazing.
她们完全是疯了一样地喜欢美国人
They absolutely love Americans and they are completely fucking insane.
对,是阿, 如果她们真的想和你发生什么的话
Yeah, well, they have to be if they want anything to do with you.
- 所以, 阿曼达 - 喔,对啦
- So, Amanda. - Yeah, okay.
- 怎么了?克里斯! - 我就知道你会问
- What? Chris! - I knew This was coming.
别这样
Come on.
罗伯在我们预定到这来的三礼拜前跟她分手了...
Rob literally broke up with her three weeks before we were supposed...
所以娜塔莉拖着她的屁股把她拉上了飞机
to come out here and Natalie had to drag her ass onto the airplane.
太好了!看看她
Perfect! Look at her.
她很孤单,而且她在欧洲
She's lonely, she's in Europe.
忘掉前男友最好的方法就是狂欢 我非常乐意奉陪
Best way to get over an ex is with a fling. I could be her fling.
- 你真是个变态的王八蛋 - 我才不变态 兄弟!
- You're a sick son-of-a-bitch. - I'm not sick, dude!
你可以冷静点吗?
Would you stop?
- 我和她有机会吗? - 不 你没有
- Do I have A shot with her? - No, you don't.
- 不行? 你确定 - 没机会 好吗
- No? All right. - Zero. Fine.
-我不会打扰她的 -谢谢了
- I'll leave it alone. - Thank you.
你和娜塔莉呢? 你们还是很好吧?
What about you and Natalie? You guys going good?
你用这种眼神看我很恐怖喔,兄弟
It's creepy when you look at me like that, dude.
帮我拿着
Hold this.
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
你是认真的?
太好了, 兄弟!
Yeah, dude!
我还没付诸实行 但我打算在莫斯科跟她求婚
I haven't asked her yet. I'm gonna propose in Moscow.
- 会有什么让她迟疑吗? - 啊 我希望没有
- Does she have any idea? - Ah, well, I hope not.
- 阿曼达知道吗? - 不知道
- What about Amanda? - No.
真是太棒了, 兄弟
That's awesome, dude.
重返车诺比 鬼城实录
我真不敢相信
Unbelievable.
真她妈一场暴动
A fucking riot.
喔, 真谢谢你了 这真是个美好的晚上
Oh, man, thank you so much. This was such a good night.
是阿,没错
Yeah, it was.
告诉过你了,伙计  喔 回公寓再来吧  不然开个房间也好
Told you, man. Okay. Save it for the apartment. Get a room!
去城里吧,我们可是在欧洲! 别听他的
Go to town, we're in Europe! Don't listen to him.
- 哇! 你没事吧? - 哈!谢谢你,我好得很
- Whoa! You all right? - Hello! Thank you, good save.
小心点! 这些鹅卵石会绊倒你的
Watch out! These cobblestones, they'll get you.
谢谢你这个好主人 真的很好玩
Thank you for being a good host. We've had a lot of fun.
我的荣幸 你喜欢在基辅的自己?
My pleasure. You enjoying yourself in Kiev?
我喜欢!是啊 这真是个美丽的小城
I am! Yes, it's a beautiful little city.
- 真的不错, 对吧? - 对,这里太棒了
- It's not bad, right? - Yeah, it's great.
等你到了莫斯科
Wait till Moscow.
等你到了莫斯科再说 你相信我吗?
Wait until you get to Moscow. You believe me?
我不知道
I don't know.
你相信我吗? 我可不太相信你的高跟鞋 来
Do you trust me? I don't trust you in those heels. Come here.
- 保罗. 把手拿开! - 抱歉
- Paul. Hands off! - Sorry.
- 你有麻烦了 - 我有麻烦了!
- You're trouble. - I am trouble!
我不能保证在路的尽头会发生什么,可是...
I can't promise what's gonna happen at the end of the road, but...
别摔倒了
Don't fall.
这些台阶很滑
Those stairs are slippery.
拜托, 晚上锁好你的门 我不相信他
Please, lock your door tonight. I don't trust him.
-克里斯多夫. -有
- Christopher. - Yeah.
- 你跑来基辅找你兄弟 - 是啊, 我总是追随着你
- You are visiting your brother in Kiev. - Yeah, well, I had to chase you down.
我不知道你是什么时候定的行程 还是张单程票
I didn't know when you booked this trip, it was a one-way ticket.
我很想念你 伙计
I missed you, buddy.
是啊,我也很想你 见到你真是太好了
Yeah, I missed you too, man. It's good to see you.
- 家里如何? 很好吧? - 是啊,家里都好
- How are things back home? Good? - Yeah, things are great.
妈还是很担心, 当然 你知道她的
Mom's worried sick, of course. You know how she is.
你有跟爸说吗?
You spoken to Dad?
没, 我, 嗯...没.
No, I, uh... No.
- 你该打个电话给他 - 我知道我应该
- You should call him. - I know I should.
- 保罗,我们该往哪走? - 左边
- Paul, which way should we go? - Left.
嘿, 嘿, 嘿, 我们不想惹麻烦 说真的
Hey, hey, hey, we don't want any trouble, seriously.
- 别碰我 - 别这样
- Don't touch me. - Come on.
- 晚安 - 祝你晚安
- Good night. - Have a good night.
晚安 Bye-bye.
Good night. Bye-bye.
走吧 走吧 走吧
Come on, come on, come on.
- 该死的输家 - 真是友好的人们
- Fucking losers. - Real friendly people here.
别管这些了 明天可是个大日子
Don't worry about it. We got a big day tomorrow.
好吧,我猜这应该是早餐的菜单?  可是我不确定
Okay, I'm assuming that this is the breakfast menu? But I don't know.
不好意思,这里...
Excuse me, is...
好吧, 她还没喝她的早安咖啡
Yeah, she hasn't had her coffee yet.
保罗跑哪去了?他应该要帮我们搞定这些的
Where's Paul? He's supposed to help us with this.
我不知道,我只是想来点油腻的东西
I don't know, I just want something greasy.
你能帮我找出些油腻的东西吗, 拜托?
Can you just point out something greasy, please?
你需要宿醉特餐
You need the Hangover Special.
阿曼达, 我要为保罗昨晚的行为道歉
Amanda, I want to apologize for Paul's behaviour last night.
喔,不用啦 他人很好 我是说... 我了解他这样的人, 你懂吗?
Oh, please. He's fine. I mean, I know the type, you know?
都是嘴上谈兵
Just all talk.
是啊,不过, 有时候他不只是说说而已
Yeah, well, with him, it's not always just talk.
我能应付他, 我不会担心的  你知道吗?
I can handle him, I'm not too worried about it. You know?
而且我敢肯定,在他的内心深处...
And I'm sure, deep down in there...
- 非常深, 非常非常深... - 的某处...
- Very deep down, very... - Somewhere...
他是个好人,你知道吗? 只是他没表现出来, 就这样
he's a good guy, you know? It's just an act, that's all.
我在想,他是你的血亲,宝贝 而你却跟他完全不同
I mean, he's related to you, baby, and you turned out all right.
- 那倒是 - 是啊, 你最棒了
- That's true. - Yeah, you're okay.
我说真的 如果你要我踢他屁股的话 只要跟我说一声
That's true. Just let me know if I need to kick his ass for you.
- 谢谢你, 老兄 哈! - 早啊 小鬼头们
- Thanks, dude. Hello! - Morning, children.
- 你跑去做啥了? - 哈
- How are you doing? - Hello.
- 你还好吗? - 好到不行
- How are you? - Fantastic.
嗯,我知道我说过我们要去莫斯科了
So, I know I said we're going to Moscow.
但我想要问你们一个问题, 而且我需要你们的答案
But I'm gonna ask you a question, and I want an answer.
答案是否定的
The answer is already no.
你们听过车诺比吗?
You guys ever heard of Chernobyl?
- 有 - 有
- Yeah. - Yeah.
那里不是发生了什么核子灾害吗?
Isn't that where the nuclear disaster happened?
是啊 我遇到了一个很酷的家伙 尤里, 有谁...
Yes. I met this really cool guy, Uri, who's a...
你们听过 极限旅游吗?
Have you heard of extreme tourism?
怎么说呢,没听过 没有
Somehow, I haven't, no.
你们知道我们要去哪了 对吧?
You guys see where this is going, right?
我们要去莫斯科 跟我们说过的一样
We're going to Moscow, as we talked about.
克里斯?可以让我说完吗?
Chris? Can I please finish?
总之 那是一个叫皮里亚特的小镇 就在车诺比的旁边
So, there's this place called Pripyat. It's a town right next to Chernobyl.
尤里,我们的极限导游将很高兴的带我们到那里
Uri, who is very excited to take us there, is an extreme tour guide.
他会向我们展示这个一夜之间被废弃的城市
He's gonna show us this city that was abandoned overnight.
正确地来说 他们没有时间做任何的处置
Literally. They had no time to take anything.
工厂，学校，商店，住宅， 公寓，一切都还是存在的
Factories, schools, stores, homes, apartments, everything's still there.
想想看你能在那里拍到什么照片, 阿曼达?
Imagine the photo shoot you can have there, Amanda?
是的, 但是...那些辐射线什么的呢?
Yeah, but, radiation levels or something.
- 这可能有点危险 对吧? - 我们只在那待一天而已
- It's probably pretty dangerous, right? - We're only gonna be there for a day.
不过几个小时,看看那些很酷的东西 然后我们就闪了
A few hours, see some cool shit and then we split.
- 我们要怎么去? - 尤里会搞定
- How are we gonna get there? - Uri's gonna take us.
- 他有一台面包车 - 面包车?
- He's got a van. - A van?
- 对 - 他有一台面包车?
- Yeah. - He has A van?
他有一台面包车!
He has a van!
好吧...
Okay...
除了你只大致提到的面包车的状况之外...
Aside from the sketchy van situation...
如果你保证 这是个安全的旅游...
and if you promise that this tour is safe...
我想这可能是挺酷的
I think it could be kinda cool.
- 这就是我说的 - 你是在开玩笑吧
- That's what I'm talking about. - You're kidding.
不是啦 我是说他也许是对的
No. I mean-I don't know. He's right.
我们都到了欧洲,我们何不...
We're in Europe, we might as well...
尽我们所能的 多看看这里的不同东西
see as much as we possibly can while we're here.
我不知道
I don't know.
-告诉我你不想见见尤里. -我不想见到尤里.
- Tell me you don't want to meet Uri. - I don't want to meet Uri.
你怎么能这么说? 你根本都没见过他
How can you say that? You haven't even met him yet.
好吧, 我们拍些照片,走走逛逛, 然后回到原本的行程
Okay, we'll take some pictures, explore a bit, and then we'll be on our way.
一如原本的计画 对吧?
Just as planned. Right?
我不太喜欢你跟他一鼻孔出气
I don't like that he's rubbing off on you.
他只能从他自己鼻孔出气
He's definitely not rubbing off.
你真是让人难以置信,你知道吗?
You're incredible, you know that?
好吧,就让我们举手表决吧,好吗?
All right, let's just settle this by a show of hands, please?
谁要跟保罗来去车诺比?
Who's coming with Paul to Chernobyl?
- 帅! - 你是跟我开玩笑, 对吧?
- Yeah! - You're kidding me, right?
你们真是太软弱了
You guys are so weak.
太好了,小朋友们!欢迎来到尤里的极限旅游团  让我们上吧!
All right, kids! Welcome to Uri's Extreme Travel. Let's do it.
欢迎来到尤里旅游
Welcome to Uri's Extreme.
尤里!
Uri!
还好吗, 老兄?
What's up, buddy?
早啊
Good morning.
- 请进! 欢迎 欢迎 -好啦 老兄!我们整团在这了
- Come in! Welcome, welcome. - All right, man! The gang is all here.
- 这是我老弟 克里斯. - 你好吗?
- This is my little brother Chris. - How You doing?
他的女友娜塔莉. 这是可爱的阿曼达.
His girlfriend Natalie. The lovely Amanda.
-各位,这是尤里. - 嗨
- Guys, this is Uri. - Hi.
哈
Hello.
总之,我告诉他们我们今天要做点小小冒险...
So, I was telling them about our little adventure today...
但是克里斯是个乖乖牌,跟平常一样
and Chris got parental, as usual.
所以我想要你能给他一点安全感...
So I figured you'd give him a little peace of mind...
在他尿湿裤子之前...
before he pisses his pants.
- 你会, 嗯, 紧张吗? - 不 我不会 我并不紧张
- You're feeling, uh, nervous? - No, I'm not. I'm not nervous.
你这里是一家很棒的店 这里很...嗯...专业
It's a nice shop you got here, it's very, uh, professional.
谢谢你 那是我最在意的事
Thank you. It's all mine.
- 这是你的店? - 是啊,挺不赖
- It's all yours, huh? - Yeah, very nice.
- 是的,这是我的店 - 嗯, 你是...退役军人?
- Yes, it's all mine. - Well, what are you, ex-military?
对,特种部队
Yes, Special Forces.
那重要吗? 就算他是个该死的魔术师又如何,兄弟?
What does it matter if he's a fuckin' magician, dude?
我只是随便问个该死的问题罢了
I'm just asking a fucking question.
好吧 尤里,我们今天的计画是什么? 我们要做些什么?
Okay. Uri, what's the plan for today? What are we doing?
好的,这是一个很好的团体旅游行程
Well, this is a very well organized tour.
我为特别有冒险精神的游客设计好 有一段时间了...
I've been taking special adventurous tourists for a while now...
所以你会体验到非常... 你会怎么说?
so you should feel very, how do you say?
- 特别? - 特别! 我喜欢这个词
- Special? - Special, I like that.
好了, 试着想想有一座没有人的城市 完全是属于你的
Okay, so imagine, you have big city and no one's there. All to yourself.
这样安全吗?
Is it safe?
当然安全 这可不是我第一次带团 娜塔莉卡
Of course it's safe. This is not my first rodeo, Natalika.
-不好意思我们迟到了! -我们到了
- So sorry we're late! - We're here.
嘿, 你们也是要去特殊旅游团的 对吧?
Hey, you guys are for the special tour, yeah?
是啊!
Yeah!
我是麦可,这是我的维京人柔依.
I'm Michael, this is my Viking Zoe.
你好吗?我是克里斯 很高兴认识你
How you doing? Chris. Nice to meet.
你好吗?我是保罗. 很高兴认识你, 老兄
What's up, man? I'm Paul. Nice to meet you, buddy.
- 好吧, 我们出发! - 出发啦
- Okay, we go! - We go now.
- 走吧 走吧 - 走
- Come, come. - All right.
漂亮
Sweet.
- 我们没害你们等太久吧? - 不会 你们别担心
- We didn't keep you waiting? - No. You guys are fine.
柔依,不是跟你说了!跟着大队走!
Zoe, I told you! Go with the flow!
那么,告诉我吧, 维京人是怎么回事?
So, tell me, what's up with the whole Viking thing?
他老是这样叫我 我是挪威来的,所以...
He calls me that all the time. I'm from Norway, so...
而他呢 是我的澳洲冲浪好手
And he's my Australian surfer dude.
好啦, 让我们摇滚吧!
All right, let's rock and roll!
来啦
Yes.
耶, 兄弟们!这是在开玩笑吗?
Yeah, buddy! Are you kidding?
我们要坐这个去?
That's what we're riding in?
- 也有可能是... 用滚的过去 - 把背包放后面
- Might as well just... roll with it. - Put your bags in the back.
第一次去那?
First time there?
皮里亚特?对啊 你们呢?
Pripyat? Yeah. How about you guys?
是啊 有个家伙说去那看看是很神奇的
Yes. Someone said that it's pretty fantastic.
- 你们俩是来甜心月? - "甜心月" '?
- You two sweethearts moonin'? - "Moonin" '?
你是说?- 蜜月
Are we what?- Honeymooning.
是啊, 完全正确 我们是来度蜜月的
Yeah, actually, we are honeymooning.
我们只能"勉强"算是朋友
We're just friends. Barely.
你真不可爱
You're cute.
- 你们呢? - 喔, 我们相爱一辈子了
- Are you guys? - Oh, yeah, we're timeless.
一个月
A month.
你们才在一起一个月? 上帝保佑
You guys have only been together a month? God bless.
那两个跟结了婚没两样
These two are practically married.
- 出发 - 收到!
- We go. - Shotgun!
谢谢你
Thank you.
有人饿了吗?  我这有牛肉干
Anybody gets hungry, I have beef jerky.
皮里亚特从这过去只要两小时 而车诺比就在那附近
Pripyat is two hours from here, and Chernobyl is not far from there.
一定很好玩!
Good time!
车诺比到底是发生了什么?
What exactly happened in Chernobyl?
一个失败的系统测试造成了车诺比事件
The Chernobyl disaster was a result of failed systems tests.
那导致了能量暴增
It caused sudden power surge.
然后4号反应炉变成了空气
And reactor number four became one with the air.
- 变成空气? - 蒸发掉了
- One with the air? - Vaporized.
它爆炸了
It exploded.
不好意思, 那是说什么?
I'm sorry, what does that mean?
尘归尘土归土了
Nature has reclaimed its rightful home.
我们到了
Here we are.
欢迎来到皮里亚特.
Welcome to Pripyat.
照相吧
Photo.
我们现在要进入禁区
We're now entering exclusion zone.
待在这里多久时间内是安全的?
How long is it safe to be here?
这里很安全的 我们只会在皮里亚特待两个钟头
It's very safe. We'll only be in Pripyat for two hours.
这是哪里? 看起来像是个检查哨?
What is this place? Is it like a checkpoint?
看起来是
Looks like it.
为什么一个废弃的城市还要设检查哨?
Why would there be a checkpoint at an abandoned town?
游客
Tourists.
好吧...
Okay...
- 我去跟他们说说 - 你们觉得如何?
- Let me do the talking. - Well, you think?
- 把相机放下 - 喔, 知道了
- Put your cameras away. - Yeah, got it.
你看那边那家伙
Look at this guy over there.
- 那些家伙 - 嗯 那些家伙看起来很认真啊
- That guy's... s. - Yeah. These guys look pretty serious.
我不知道他们在说什么 不过我看那家伙是说不行
I don't know what they're saying, but this guy is saying no.
看这家伙
Look at this guy.
你看到底是怎么了?
What do you think is going on?
真恐怖!
It's scary!
天啊, 你看那家伙 有够魁武的
God, look at that guy. He's huge.
- 谢啦,宝贝 - 你在干嘛
- Thanks, baby. - Come on, you.
把自己藏起来 不让他看到 如何?
Hide me so he doesn't see me. How's that?
- 你在享受犯罪的快感吗? - 我是这样的人吗?
- You have a criminal soul? - Do I look like one of them?
今天正好不能让我们过去 有些东西在维修
He is not letting us in today. There's maintenance going on.
维修? 我记得你说那城市都荒废了
Maintenance work? I thought you said this place was abandoned.
的确很奇怪
It is unusual.
一般来说,他们会先告诉我啊...
Usually, they let me know in advance...
除非是真的有什么事发生
if something like this is going to happen.
等等, 我记得你说你会搞定的
Wait, I thought you said everything was gonna be taken care of.
- 我们可是已经付了钱了,老兄 - 我知道 我知道
- We paid for this tour, bro. - I know, I know.
不用担心
Don't worry.
还有别条路能进皮里亚特.
There's more than one way into Pripyat.
那就走吧
Make it happen.
真是挺奇怪的,我连一只鸟或是任何生物都没看到
It's so bizarre, I don't see any birds or anything.
这就是尤里专属的特别入口
This must be Uri's special entrance.
保罗, 这看起来真他妈的随便
Paul, this looks fuckin' sketchy, man.
别再装小孬孬了 我们都已经到了, 享受一下吧, 好吗?
Stop being a pussy. We came all this way, enjoy yourself, all right?
那是叫做明智
It's called being sensible.
这样不好吧 朋友们
This is not right, you guys.
我们搞不好最后会进乌克兰的监狱
We're gonna end up in a Ukrainian jail or something.
来吧, 别忘了这是个冒险
Come on, just think of it as an adventure.
没问题的
It's okay.
- 这真是太棒了 - 你真的这么想?
- This is the awesomest. - Really?
好了, 没问题啦 皮里亚特今天是我们的了
Okay, no problem. Today we have Pripyat to ourselves.
- 漂亮 - 太好了
- Sweet. - All right.
我们走吧
Here we go.
我没想到这里还有湖
I was not expecting a lake out here.
皮里亚特到了
And there is Pripyat.
工人们都是从这里到车诺比去工作
Home to the workers and families of Chernobyl.
真是不可思议
It's incredible.
抓好! 接下来会有一点颠簸
Hold on! This is going to be a little bumpy.
一点颠簸
A little bumpy.
喔, 你不如干脆...
Oh, you're not gonna...
让我们"下"去用走的!
And down we go!
或"上"!
And up!
喔 我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
安全带原来就是为了这种事设计的?
When are you putting seat belts in this thing?
- 耶稣 - 还有呕吐袋
- Jesus. - Or barf-bags.
真是太夸张了
It's ridiculous.
Ok  现在呢,我要给你们看看水里面的某种东西
Okay. Now, I want to show you something in water.
他要我们看看水里面的某种东西
He wants to show us something in water.
谢啦
Thank you.
你先请 你先请
After you. After you.
- 保持在我身后 - 说的好像我们要干嘛似的
- Stay close behind me. - Like we're gonna go anywhere.
- 保罗? - 嗯?
- Paul? - Yeah?
我想麻烦你 如果看到水里有东西在动 赶快告诉我 Ok?
I want you to tell me if you see something moving in water. Okay?
Ok...
Okay...
别把鞋子弄湿了
You don't want to get your booties wet.
手给我! 手给我!
Give me your hand! Give me your hand!
你没事吧? 你没事吧, 伙计?
You okay? You okay, mate?
搞笑啊, 混蛋
Funny, bugger.
- 你他妈的耍我? - 他真他妈的搞笑
- Are you fucking kidding me? - He's a fucking comedian.
- 这是个玩笑 - 玩笑 你玩蛋啦
- It's jerky. - Jerky, you jerk.
嘿,大伙, 能走了吗, 拜托?
Hey, GUYS, can we go, please?
- 他妈的骗到我了! - 对 他也骗到我了
- Fucking got me! - Yeah. He got me, too.
喔,该死!
Oh, shit!
那是个玩笑
It was a joke.
不好意思
Sorry about that.
这边有好看的
Come have look at this.
不会是另一个玩笑吧?
Is this another joke?
不 不是 来这吧
No. No, come.
哇哩咧
Holy cow.
- 别靠太近 - 为什么? 应该是死的
- Don't get too close. - Why? It's dead.
- 好恶心 - 它脸上长了锯齿
- It's disgusting. - Look at the chompers on him.
那是什么东西?
What is that thing?
摸摸看,伙计
Touch it, mate.
现在谁才是小孬孬, 啊?
Who's the pussy now, huh?
- 能走了吗? 这真的好恶心 - 别动它
- Can we go? This is disgusting. - Keep it up.
走吧? 这真的好恶
Can we go? That's disgusting.
- 真是超威的 - 继续走吧
- That's awesome. - And moving on.
看到那牙齿了吗? 超酷的,对吧?
See its teeth? It's cool, huh?
喔, 我的天!
Oh, my God!
- 你刚刚那个玩笑有押韵喔, 尤里? - 当然
- Did you just make a rhyme, Uri? - Yes.
开个小玩笑
Make small joke.
- 免除烦恼 - 这就是尤里.
- Not to worry. - Here is Uri.
那么, 尤里,这地方被遗弃多久了?
So, Uri, how long has this place been abandoned?
有25年了 直到最近辐射剂量下降了
It's been 25 years. Only recently have radiation levels gone down.
这真是疯狂 这真是该死的毛骨悚然
Man, this is crazy. It's creepy as fuck.
我们得回到主要道路上 那是唯一一条离开皮里亚特的路
We are back on main road. It's only way in and out of Pripyat.
嗯, 除了你的快速通关道,是吗?
Yeah, except for your shortcut, right?
在车诺比工作的家庭都住在这里
This is where the families Chernobyl lived.
- 懂吗? - 嗯
- See? - Yeah.
- 他们都集中在这 - 是啊 非常可怜
- These were all full at one point. - Yes. Very sad.
有5万多人被迫离开
Fifty thousand people, families, just left.
Ok, 坐好 有点颠簸,有点颠簸
Okay, hold on. Little bump, little bump.
- 摩天轮 - 好了
- The Ferris. - All right.
- 我爱死这里的东西了 - 我们到了
- I used to love those things. - We're here.
还想着回家吗,克里斯?
Still want to go home, Chris?
我很高兴我们来了这里 谢谢了
I'm happy we're here. Thanks.
- 你太客气了 - 我们走吧 友爱两兄弟
- You're welcome. - There we go. Brotherly love.
大伙 看这!
Guys, look at this.
哇
Ah, man.
Ok, 各位
Okay, everyone.
别离开我太远 就会很安全的
Stay near me and you'll be safe.
我带着盖格计数器
I have Geiger counter.
那能让我们知道哪里的辐射剂量太高
It will let us know if the radiation levels are high.
那太好了
That's good.
这里没问题
Levels are good.
你们能想像这里曾经充满着孩子?在这里...玩耍着?
Can you guys imagine this like, full with kids? Like...playing?
- 说实话 这真的很令人悲伤 - 他们根本不知道
- It's really sad, actually. - They had no idea.
我是说 这根本让人难以置信
I mean, this is just unbelievable.
我从没见过像这样的事
I have never seen anything like this.
这就像他们正准备过狂欢节或什么的
It's like they were getting ready for a carnival or something.
他们正在准备 "五月节", 那是一个欢庆春天到来的节日
They were preparing for "May Day", the celebration of Spring.
可惜永远没得过了
Never happened.
Ok, 走吧 往这里
Okay, let's go. This way.
可以帮我们照张相吗? 尤里, 可以吗?帮我们照张相
Can we get a photo? Uri, you want to take it? A photo.
- 嘿,大伙? - 好啊 快来照相
- Hey, guys? - All right. Quick photo.
和新朋友一起
And new friends.
Ok...
Okay...
好了
Good.
真有美国风
It's so American.
走在这里, 感觉好像...
In a way, it's like...
他们还生活在这里,但是却...
There was life, and it just...
嘿, 你听到了什么吗?
Hey, you hear that?
什么都没有
Silence.
这里真的完全被自然接管了
It's like nature really has taken over.
最后一项了
One last thing.
- 要进去吗? - 是的
- Are we going in? - Yes.
那是什么,宝贝? 哇, 柔依. 嘿, 宝贝,没事的
What is it, babe? Whoa, Zoe. Hey, babe, it's okay.
它们通常不会那么接近城镇  可能是快饿死了
They usually don't come so close to town. Must have been starving.
可惜还是来错地方
I reckon he's right.
进来吧
Come in.
好恶心
That's disgusting.
这就是VIP入口的礼遇
That's the VIP entrance. Treatment.
可怜的家伙...
Poor guy...
会有其他的动物在这吗?
Are there any other animals here?
不太可能 尤其是在白天
Unlikely. Especially during the day.
除了你
Just you.
停下来
Stop it.
这里是数以千计被废弃的公寓的其中一间
Here's one of a thousand apartments that were abandoned.
酷
Cool.
这些人们只有不到五分钟的时间...
The people were not even given five minutes...
收拾他们的个人财产
to collect their personal possessions.
你可别拿这里的东西 都是受到污染的
You can't take that. It's contaminated.
我只是看看...不要好像抓到现行犯一样看我
I was just look... Spot the convict. Cheers, man.
它真的有被污染
It's contaminated.
有一段时间, 常有人来到这里 把这里给洗劫一空
For a while, people came here and they looted through these buildings.
他们把这些东西卖进黑市
They took these things, sold them on black market.
买下那些东西的人都病了...
People who bought them got sick...
却还是不知道他们是被辐射污染了
not knowing they were contaminated by radiation.
抱歉, 我真的只是...
Sorry, I was just...
来吧, 来看看这个
Come, let's have a look.
那我们待在这还呼吸什么的,没关系吗?
But it's okay to be here and breathe?
是的 没关系
Yes, yes.
我们在这里的时间不足以受到污染
We're not here long enough to get exposure.
车诺比的4号反应炉 当灾害发生的时候
Chernobyl Reactor Number Four. Where the disaster happened.
- 这可真是够近了 - 你呢 你有进去过吗?
- That's pretty close. - Have you, you been inside?
没有 你得有防辐射服才能进去
No. You can only go inside with radiation suit.
而且只能防护很短的时间
Only for short period of time.
来 拍张照吧
Here, take picture.
- 拍张甜蜜 罗曼蒂克的照片? - 好了 好了
- Take a nice, romantic photo? - All right, all right.
嘿,我不是叫你过去...
Hey, I wasn't gonna...
- 嗯 他来了 - 这可以贴在冰箱上
- Yeah, he was. - This is going on the fridge.
这是一个比喻 顺便说一下 伙计们
That's a metaphor here, by the way, guys.
别告诉我
Do tell.
- 这真是太美了 - 我们的爱是爆炸式增长
- That's beautiful. - Our love is just exploding.
喔,天啊
Oh, God.
这是辐射威胁之下唯一的好事
The one good thing about the radiation...
我想你终于长出了一只老二
is that I'll probably finally grow a penis.
你们可真搞笑
These guys are funny.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
- 来个最佳一吻吧? - 什么?
- Can you beat that kiss? - What?
我们该走了
We should go now.
这里很快就会天黑了, 我们得快点回到面包车上
It's going to get dark soon, we should get back to van before then.
那他妈的是什么?
Fuck was that?
是喔,新把戏吗
Right, it's gonna be a trick.
等着
Stay.
那他妈是啥?
Fuck is that?
哇操!跑 跑 跑!
Holy shit! Go, go, go!
- 天啊! - 你娘咧!
- Jesus! - Motherfucker!
喔, 天啊!
Oh, my God!
操!
Fuck!
- 大家都没事吧? - 别他妈待在这里!
- Is everyone okay? - Don't fucking stand there!
赶快离开, 动起来 动起来 动起来!
Let's go, move, move, move!
走!
Go!
操! 那他妈到底是什么?
Fuck! What the fuck was that?
走 走
Go, go.
黑熊或是他妈的棕熊吧? 喔, 天啊!
Black bear or it's a fucking brown bear? Oh, Jesus!
- 熊在那里做什么? -我们可以他妈的先离开这再说吗?
- What is a bear doing here? - Can we just get the fuck out of here?
- 哎呀 - 小心一点
- Jeez. - Watch out for that.
喔, 操!
Oh, fuck!
- Ok - 该死的
- Okay. - Holy shit.
- 我们可以他妈的快点闪人吗? - 是啊
- Can we just get the fuck out of here? - Yes.
- 可真谢谢你了 - 是啊 别客气了
- Thanks for that. - Yeah. Don't mention it.
我说过这会让人兴奋的,难道不是吗?
Told you it'd be exciting, didn't I?
是啊,兴奋到可能会死...
Yeah, almost getting mauled to death...
而且还是被只从地狱来的辐射熊干掉? 真他妈令人兴奋
by a radioactive bear from hell? It's pretty exciting.
其他人能有这样的故事吗?
Anybody else have a story like this?
- 好笑吗 - 你没事吧?
- Funny. - You okay?
有人拍到照片吗?
Anyone get a photo?
照片...这家伙
A photo. This guy.
天啊
Jesus.
熊! 熊,熊!我瞎掰的
Bear! Bear, bear! I'm kidding.
你这坏蛋
That's bad.
那么, 尤里, 其他动物们, 都在树林里,啊?
So, Uri, all the animals, they stay in the woods, huh?
这很不寻常
It's very unusual.
我已经做了五年 从来没有见过这样的事
I've been doing this for five years. I've never seen anything like this.
可真让人沮丧, 是吧?
It's kind of chilly out here, huh?
有过狗, 有过狼 但是熊...很奇怪
A dog, a wolf. But a bear, very odd.
- 但很过瘾 对吧? - 那倒是 伙计
- It was exciting, right? - Yeah, mate.
被熊袭击我就不另外收费了
No extra charge for bear attack.
向皮里亚特说再见吧
Say goodbye to Pripyat.
- 再见 - 是啊, 再见 再见
- Ciao. - Yeah, ciao-ciao.
嘿,克里斯多夫?
Hey, Christopher?
莫斯科! 谢谢你
Moscow! Thank you.
- 可以给我你的e-mail吗? - 当然了 老兄
- I'll have to get your e-mail, eh? - Yeah, for sure, dude.
- 上瘾了吗? 我会回基辅的 - 说定了 老兄
- Catch up again? I'll be back to Kiev. - Done, dude.
- 这可真够爽的 - 真的很过瘾
- It was a blast. - It's been a pleasure.
开个暖气吧 老兄
Turn the heater on, buddy.
油门
Pump it.
给它多点油
Give it some gas.
- 怎么了,还有油吧? - 有啊 油箱还有一半
- What's up, is there gas in there? - Yes. Half a tank.
那怎么发不动 伙计?
Is it the starter, mate?
以前发生过吗?
Has this happened before?
我猜这里应该没有Triple A修车场吧?
I don't suppose you guys have Triple A out here?
你手机有信号吗?
Do you have reception?
一整天都没信号,各位 服务区域应该没涵盖这里
I haven't had reception all day, guys. There's no kind of reception out here.
看 看
Look, look.
你们他妈的在干嘛,伙计?
What the fuck could've done that, mate?
这他妈的是被咬断的
That's fucking been chewed on.
- 等等 发生了什么事? - 到底怎么了?
- Wait, what's happening? - What's going on?
- 车子的线路挂了 - 被咬断了
- The wires have been destroyed. - Chewed on.
咬断是什么意思? 什么,被什么咬断? 动物吗?
What do you mean chewed on? What, by what? An animal?
什么样的动物会吃汽车零件?
What kind of animal chews on car parts?
你确定真的只有我们在这里吗?
Are you sure we're out here alone?
是啊 你也听到早上那些士兵说了,这里是禁区
Yes. You heard the soldiers this morning, this place is off-limits.
这里只有我们
We are here alone.
这他妈怎么回事, 麦可?
What the fuck is it, Michael?
火心塞的引线被咬断了...
That's the spark-plug leads, been chewed on...
- 你能找人来修吗? - 被浣熊 老鼠 或是其他动物弄的?
- Can you call someone? - By a raccoon, a rat, or some animal.
但是怎么会有动物在这里?
But how would an animal get in here?
从车子下面 经过引擎
Under the car. Through the engine.
- 从车底? - 是啊 是啊
- Underneath? - Yeah, yeah.
他正在问附近有没能协助发生突发事故的人...
He said there aren't any around here and all of a sudden...
我不懂
I don't know.
各位!能先静静让他能... 我们正试着要  要...
Guys! Let's just shut up and let him- We're trying to-to...
他妈的
Fuck me.
尤里?
Uri?
有什么计画吗 ?
What's the plan, mate?
嘿 大个子? 有什么计画吗?
Hey, big fella? What's the plan?
我好饿, 感觉快死了
I'm so hungry, I could die.
哇啦,这下可好
Well, this is great.
把关于这个该死的旅游的一切都交给你 先生
Gotta hand it to you. Some fucking tour, mister.
- 这可不是我的错 - 哦，真的吗？不是你的错吗？
- This is not my fault. - Oh, really? Not your fault?
因为根据我的记忆 你就是那个带我们来这的人
Cause last time I checked, you were the one that drove us out here.
如果不是有你的话 我们根本不会在这里
Well, if it weren't for you, we wouldn't be here either.
喔 我真是不应该帮你们找乐子
Oh, I'm sorry to try and show you guys some fun...
-而且还是当你们自己跑来找我时候 -喔 是啊 真是有趣极了
- while you're out here visiting me. - Oh, yeah. Lot of fun.
嘿,克里斯. 没事的,你知道吗?
Hey, Chris. All right, you know what?
放轻松点
Relax.
- 我们都没事 - 我们他妈的困在这咧
- We're fine. - We're fucking stranded out here.
所以别叫我放轻松
And don't tell me to relax.
我向天发誓...
I swear to God...
这是我最后一次听从你那些该死的蠢点子
this is the last time I listen to one of your dumb fuckin' ideas.
嘿,你知道吗,克里斯?  你就光在这废话对我们也没啥帮助
Hey, you know what, Chris? Your fucking whining isn't helping right now.
-他有生气的权利 -好了 大家别吵  嘿 尤里
- He's got every right to be pissed. - Okay, guys. Hey, Uri.
有人会知道我们在这吧,是吗?
Someone has to know we're out here, right?
我是一人公司
I work alone.
真他妈的太好了
Fucking great.
那 告诉我 尤里
So, tell me, Uri.
我们现在还有些甚么选项?
What are our options right now?
我们可以留在车里
We stay in van.
- 在这里安全吗? - 是的 这里是安全的
- Are we safe here? - Yes, we're safe.
我们关上窗 锁上门
We close windows, lock doors.
到了早上 我把车子修好 然后回去 或是我们走回那个检查哨
In morning, I fix van, we drive up. Or we all walk back to checkpoint.
等等 等等 不好意思
Wait, wait, I'm sorry.
你的意思是我们得在这里过夜吗?
Are you suggesting that we spend the night here?
Ok, ok, 大伙
Okay, okay, guys
不好意思 我们真的得快点离开 好吗?
I'm sorry, but we're gonna have to hike outta here, all right?
尤里, 怎么能走到那个检查哨?
Uri, how far to the checkpoint?
- 那有20公里远 - 那大约是12, 13英哩
- It's 20 kilometers. - That's like 12, 13 miles.
太好了 我们可以走的到
Exactly. We can hike that.
不行 不行 不能在晚上!
No, no, not at night!
- 那不安全 - 安静!
- It is not safe. - Be quiet!
那他妈的是什么?
What the fuck was that?
- 有其他人在这里吗? - 那是不可能的
- Are there people here? - It's impossible.
这声音听起来像是小婴儿
It sounds like a baby.
- 到底是什么? - 那不是婴儿
- What is that? - It's not a baby.
那那个他妈的是什么, 尤里?
Then what the fuck is it, Uri?
哇 哇 有需要拿枪吗 老兄?
Whoa, whoa. What's with the gun, man?
- 你对这有疑问吗? - 对 为啥要他妈的拿枪出来?
- You have problem? - Yeah. What's with the fucking gun?
你应该要很高兴我有这个的
You should all be glad I have this.
都待在这里别出来
Everyone stay here.
- 枪耶? - 他要去哪?
- A gun? - Where is he going?
你相信他吗?
Do you trust him?
- 你要跟他一起去吗? - 放轻松 兄弟
- Do you want to go out there with him? - Easy, bro.
我不知道, 只是这...
I don't know, it's just that the...
待在这里 我去找他回来
Stay here. He'll come back.
-克里斯, 你他妈干嘛...? -他去哪?
- Chris, what the fuck...? - Where's he going?
-克里斯, 我跟你一起去 -不行, 我不要你跟我一起去
- Chris, I'm coming with you. - No, I don't want you to come with me.
你就给我待在车里 想想看有没有办法...
Just sit in the car and think of another way...
能让你他妈的成熟一点
you can fuck this up even further.
我向天发誓, 保罗,当你的兄弟真的是有够倒楣的
I swear to God, Paul, it's a fucking hazard having you as a brother.
克里斯!
Chris!
- 他要去做甚么? - 我不知道 宝贝
- What's he gonna do? - I don't know, babe.
- 他去哪了? - 尤里, 怎么了!
- Where is he going? - Uri, wait up!
我看不到他了 你们有看到他吗?
I can't see him. Can you guys see him?
喔 天啊
Oh, God.
克里斯!
Chris!
-克里斯!克里斯! -克里斯! 不!
- Chris! Chris! - Chris! No!
喔,我的天,克里斯,不!
Oh, my God, Chris, no!
你有看到什么吗?
Can you see anything?
- 你看得到他们吗? - 我不知道 我看不见
- Can you see them? - I don't know. I can't see.
克里斯!
Chris!
麦可,你有看到吗?
Michael, can you see?
开门!
Open the door!
让他进来,让他进来!
Get him in, get him in!
克里斯! 喔 我的天,克里斯!
Chris! Oh, my God, Chris!
Okay, look at me. Breathe, buddy. 克里斯, 伙计 保持清醒
Okay, look at me. Breathe, buddy. Chris, mate, keep breathing.
操!
Fuck!
-克里斯! 发生了甚么? - 我他妈不知道!
- Chris! What happened? - I don't fucking know!
- 他们有好多! - 尤里在哪?尤里在哪?
- There were a lot of them! - Where's Uri? Where's Uri?
克里斯
Chris.
克里斯, 尤里怎么了?
Chris, what happened to Uri?
他们抓到他了!他们他妈的抓了他!
They got him! They fucking got him!
什么东西他妈的抓了尤里?!
What the fuck got Uri?!
吸气,宝贝!
Just breathe, baby!
- 抓住他 抓住他 - 别看!
- Hold him, hold him. - Don't look!
- 急救箱在哪? 他受伤了 - 我不知道 找找看这里
- Where's your first aid kit? He's cut. - I don't know, check in here.
这是他妈的渔具!
That's fucking fishing tackle!
干!
Fuck!
操他妈的!
Holy shit!
- 那是什么?! - 离窗户远一点!
- What is that?! - Stay away from the windows!
退后!
Fuck off!
嘿,每个人都离他妈的窗户远点!
Hey, everyone away from the fucking windows!
离窗户远点
Stay away from the windows.
克里斯.克里斯, 看着我,兄弟 看着我,兄弟
Chris. Chris, look at me, buddy. Look at me, buddy.
不会有事的,兄弟
It's gonna be all right, brother.
看着我,兄弟 我就在这 好吗?
Look at me, buddy. Stay with me, all right?
- 我他妈的要离开这里！ - 我会带你回家
- Get me the fuck outta here! - I'm gonna get you home.
克里斯, 我会带你离开这里 克里斯, 看着我, 看着我
Chris, I'm gonna get you outta here. Chris, look at me, look at me.
我会带你离开这的 这灯又他妈的怎么了?
I'm gonna get you out. What the fuck is with the lights?
放轻松 电池要没电了 这台他妈的烂车要没电了
Just relax. The battery's dying. The fucking car battery is dying.
怎么会他妈的这样子?
What the fuck is going on?
- 把它绑紧 - 谁能帮我拿一下灯?
- Tie it tight. - Can somebody please hold the light?
好了 好了
Good, good.
操 抱歉 伙计
Fuck. Sorry, mate.
- 呼吸 宝贝 继续呼吸 - 呼吸 继续呼吸 伙计
- Breathe, baby, just breathe. - Breathe. Just breathe, mate.
我这里,撑住 操 我在这 伙计 继续呼吸
Here, hold it up. Fuck. Here, mate. Just breathe.
- 我很抱歉 - 别去看那里 伙计
- I'm so sorry. - Try not to look at it, mate.
呼吸 呼吸
Breathe, breathe.
我知道 我知道 我知道!
I know, I know, I know!
是太紧了一点 对不起 兄弟
It's gotta be tight, I'm sorry, brother.
对不起 宝贝
I'm so sorry, baby.
- 干你娘 又怎么了?! - 把灯关掉 把灯关掉!
- What the fuck?! - Turn off the light, turn off the light!
啊, 操 抱歉,克里斯.
Ah, fuck. Sorry, Chris.
拿着 拿着
Take it, take it.
操
Ah, fuck.
这里, 柔依 会没事的 宝贝
Here, Zoe. It'll be all right, baby.
继续呼吸, 伙计 你做得很好
Just breathe, mate. You're doing good.
- 你做得很好 - 我们会把你带离开这的
- You're doing good. - We're gonna get you out of this place.
我好冷
I'm freezing.
- 我知道 - 操!
- I know. - Fuck!
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
没事的 宝贝
It's okay, baby.
- 你觉得如何? - 他需要医生
- How are You feeling? - He needs a doctor.
我知道他需要医生
I know he needs a doctor.
你觉得如何?
How are you doing?
我只想他妈的快点离开这里
I just want to get the fuck out of here.
我修不好 对不起 对不起 这些线路都腐烂了
I can't fix it. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, the, the leads have rotted.
我是说, 如果我们能找到一些新的线路 那就能发动车子了 只是...
I mean, if we could get some new leads, we could roll-start it, but...
我是不是他妈的见过这个 试试看吧
I ain't fuckin' seen this before. Try it.
尤里, 这里是保罗. 听得到我吗?
Uri, this is Paul. Can you hear me?
-有别只对讲机吗? -嗯
- That the other walkie? - Yeah.
尤里, 你还在吗? 听得到我吗?
Uri, are you there? Can you hear me?
拜托
Come on.
- 好吧 我去找他 - 你根本不熟悉这里
- All right, I'm gonna go look for him. - You don't know your way around.
但是他熟 他能带我们离开这里
But he does. He can help us get out of here.
要是那些狗又回来了呢?
And what if the dogs come back?
尤里说那些狗只有晚上会出来
Uri said the dogs come out at night.
所以你们乖乖留在面包车上 而且把门关紧
So just stay in the van and keep the door shut.
我跟你去
I'll go with you.
不行 你不能去
No, you will not.
尤里可是个大块头 也许要两个人才能把他弄回来
Uri is a big fellow and it might take two of us to carry him back.
是啊,可如果他挂了呢?
Yeah, what if he's dead?
别那么说 尤里她妈的知道怎么离开这里
Don't say that. Uri knows how to get the fuck outta here.
我们可以顺便找新的电线...
We might find new leads...
你也看到有东西袭击了车子  他说，还有什么其他的东西在这里
You saw what attacked the car. He says that there's other things out here.
- 别说了 乖乖待在车里 - 拜托!
- Come on. Just Stay here. - Please!
- 拜托! - 等我
- Please! - Stay.
嗯, 我也去 我去帮帮他们, ok?
Yeah, I'm gonna come too. I'm gonna help these guys, okay?
好了 我们走
All right, let's go.
你待在车里, 把门关好  我们会回来接你
You stay in the car, you keep the door shut. We'll be back for you.
你会没事的 伙计 我们很快回来
You'll be all right, mate. We'll be back.
- 跟他们一起待着 帮帮他们 - 麦可,这真是太蠢了
- Stay with them. Help them. - Michael, this is stupid.
- 你为什么要去? - 我很快回来
- Why would you do that? - I'll be back.
你知道多少关于尤里的事?
How well you know Uri?
不多 你呢?
Not well. You?
一样
Same, same.
你想他还在这里吗?
You think he's still here?
天亮了 他可以离开了
It's been overnight. He could be gone.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I know.
你在想什么?
What are you thinking?
我在想攻击克里斯的那些狗
I think Chris got attacked by dogs.
狗应该不会造成那样的伤口
Dogs didn't do that.
也许是熊呢? 我的意思是 我们昨天的确是见到一只熊在公寓里面跑
Maybe a bear? I mean, we saw a bear run by us at the apartment yesterday.
- 他是说还有别的东西 - 是的，它可能是一只熊
- He said there was something else. - Yeah, and it could be a bear.
他说的应该是，有很多狗 天很黑，他被吓坏了
He said there was a lot of dogs. It was dark, he was in shock.
要再试试对讲机吗?
Try the walkie-talkie, will you?
嘿, 尤里, 有听到吗? 这里是保罗.
Hey, Uri, are you there? It's Paul.
- 走这边看看 - 尤里, 可以听到我吗?
- Lets go around here. - Uri, can you hear me?
不要分开太远而且眼睛睁大小心点 好吗?
Just stay close and keep your eyes open, all right?
我不是很相信他说的动物不会在白天出没
I don't believe him when he said that animals don't come out during the day.
我也不知道还有甚么能相信了
I don't know what to believe.
操
Fuck.
这就是昨晚他来的地方了吧?
This is where he went off last night, right?
试着找找有没他的人影 然后回面包车去
Let's just try and figure out how we get back to the van.
好点子 伙计
Good idea, mate.
再试试对讲机
Check your walkie-talkie again.
嘿, 尤里, 这里是保罗. 听的到我吗,老兄?
Hey, Uri, this is Paul. Can you hear me, buddy?
- 怎么? - 再来一次 再来一次
- What? - Do it again, do it again, do it again.
尤里, 是你吗...
Uri, do you come...
- 你听得到我吗? - 嗯
- Did You hear that? - Yeah.
该死的
Holy shit.
甚么该死的抓了他
Something fucking got him.
Ok, 我没走 我们得去看看
Okay, let's go. We need to go.
不 我们不去 伙计
No, we can't, mate.
我们得去看看他是不是还活着
We have to see if he's alive.
尤里?
Uri?
这里还好
It's okay.
这里有好多血
There's too much blood.
- 这样他不可能还活着 - 我知道 我知道
- There's no way that he's still alive. - I know, I know.
我们得理智一点 要知道走回头路也没用
We need to be smart about this. We're not going back there.
没错 我要再下去看看 别忘了 他至少还有枪
We are. I'm gonna go. Besides, he's got the gun.
他说的对
He's right.
往下走吧
Let's do it.
尤里?
Uri?
尤里!
Uri!
喔 操!
Oh, fuck!
操他妈的!
Holy shit!
看!
Look!
检查他的口袋里面
Gotta check his pockets.
- 操! 枪跑哪去了? - 喔 该死
- Shit! Where's the gun? - Oh, shit.
我找到弹夹了
Wait. I've got the clip.
把那个该死的门锁起来!
Lock the fucking door!
喔, 那他妈是什么?
Oh, what the fuck is that?
- 操你妈! - 枪 枪 枪!
- Holy shit! - Gun, gun, gun!
- 妈的，有没有子弹！ - 就在这里！
- Fuck, there's no bullets! - Right here!
好了,我弄好了! 我动手!
All right, I got it! I'll do it!
快走!
Go!
喔 该死!
Oh, shit!
那个给我!
Forget it!
干你娘咧!
Motherfucker!
快点他妈的下车 我们得他妈的快点离开
Get the fuck outta. We're getting the fuck outta here.
- 你什么意思? 你们去了哪? - 到底怎么了?
- What do you mean? Where we going? - What's going on?
- 我们得快点走 - 尤里呢? 你们找到他了吗?
- We gotta go. - Where's Uri? Did you find him?
- 是啊,我们看到了他的下场 - 什么?
- Yeah, what's left of him. - What?
他的意思是 尤里挂了
What he said, man. Uri's dead.
- 我们得快点走 不能留在这里 - 他没法走路
- We better go, we can't stay here. - He cannot walk.
我们真的不能留在这
We can't stay here.
- 我们没有选择的余地 帮帮我吧 - 他是对的
- I don't have a choice. Help me. - He's right.
- 什么? 宝贝 不! - 来吧 我来帮你
- What? Babe, no! - Come on, I'll help you.
- 啊 操 - 慢一点
- Ah, fuck. - Real slow.
- 慢慢的放下来 - 小心 小心 小心
- Just do it real slow. - Easy, easy, easy.
好了
All right.
- 操 - 慢慢放 慢慢放
- Aw, fuck. - There You go. There You go.
- 操! - 他妈的,我告诉过你 他没办法走!
- Fuck! - Goddamn it, I told you, he can't walk!
- 放回去 放回去 - 小心 小心
- Put it back up, put it back up. - Easy, easy.
- 怎么了? - 没办法了, 我们得带着他
- What's going on? - All right, we gotta carry him.
- 别他妈耍蠢了 - 我们不能把你丢在这!
- Don't be fucking stupid. - We're not gonna leave you here!
你带着我的话得花两倍时间才走得掉!
It'll take three of you to carry me and twice as long!
好 我留在这里陪你
Fine. I'm staying here with him.
- 我不会离开他的! - 好, 那我也不离开!
- I'm not leaving him! - Well, I'm not leaving him either!
你们有没有人在听我说话?
Would you listen to me?
你住在这里 你是唯一一个能跟这里人沟通的人
You live here. You're the only one that speaks the language.
去求援然后带他们回来啊
Go get help and bring it back.
我们会待在车理
We're staying in the van.
好吧
All right.
- 拿着这个 - 我们很快回来 来吧 柔依.
- Take this. - We'll be back. Come on, Zoe.
打开频道一
Stay on channel one.
如果你们有什么需要， 或是发生了什么 赶快通知我们
If you guys need anything, if anything happens, you call us.
有13英哩的路 我们现在出发 如果够快的话...
It's 13 miles. We're gonna leave now. If we hurry...
- 天黑之前我们就能回来了 - 如果你们回不来?
- we'll be back before it's dark. - What if you're not back?
拿着这个
Take it.
- 你会用吗? - 嗯 我想没问题
- You know how to use that? - Yeah, I think so.
好 我们走吧
All right, let's go.
- 保罗,等等 - 我们很快回来 伙计
- Paul, wait. - We'll be back, mate.
来吧 我们走柔依.
Come on, let's go, Zoe.
- 听着, 我很抱歉... - 好了 好了
- Look, I'm sorry... - Stop. Stop.
我会回来接你的
I'm gonna get you home.
我们会在你会用之前回来的
We'll be back before you know it.
没事的 宝贝 没事的
It's okay, babe. It's okay.
快走, 保罗 事情怎么会变成这样
Way to go, Paul. Fucked things up this time.
Ok,别想这么多 听着, 那对现况没有帮助
Okay, don't think like that. Come on, that's not helping anyone.
我他妈的弄砸了他整个生活
I've been doing this his whole fucking life.
我老是害他惹上麻烦 他都只是默默承受
I always get him into shit. He always pays for it.
尽管是这样 你还是他的哥哥啊
Well, despite all that, you're his big brother.
现在他要能离开这里 就只能指望你了 Ok?
So right now he's counting on you to get him out of this. Okay?
等等 等等!
Wait, wait!
该死的
Holy shit.
- 来吧 - 我们得找路绕过去
- Come on. - We got to find a way around.
- 麦可? - 安静
- Michael? - Stay quiet.
- 我们得绕过去 - 喔 天啊 Ok 快 快 快
- We'll loop around. - Oh, God. Okay, go. Go, go-go.
柔依, 柔依! 快来
Zoe, Zoe! Come on.
该死的
Shit. Guys.
辐射越来越强
The radiation's getting worse.
我们走
Let's go.
那是什么?看
What is that? Look.
好极了
Holly shit.
- 会有能开的吗? - 不可能 宝贝 电池一定都没电了
- Will any of them start? - No, babe, the batteries would be dead.
但是也许我们能找到一些电线 检查这些车 来吧!
We might be able to find some cables, though. Check the cars. Let's go!
操
Oh, fuck.
这里! 这里!
Wait! Wait!
天啊! 这是什么?
Jesus! What the fuck?
- 甚么人会对巴士扫射? - 我不知道 宝贝
- Who would shoot at a bus? - I don't know, babe.
军队?
The guards?
这些是射出孔
These are exit holes.
这些不是射击巴士的 而是从巴士射出去的
Whatever was shooting was shooting from the inside out.
- 我们专心找电线 可以吗? - 是
- Can we just find these cables, please? - Yeah.
保罗?
Paul?
阿曼达, 里面全是弹壳
Amanda, there's shells everywhere.
也许能在这找到枪
Maybe there's a gun in here.
嗯,找找看
Well, let's look.
Ok,等等, 别 别 来吧 我们回去找麦可和柔依.
Okay, wait, no. No. Come on, let's get back to Michael and Zoe.
如果后面有什么呢?
What if something's back there?
他妈的
Goddamn it.
什么都没有
Nothing.
喔 该死!
Oh, shit!
你没事吧?
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
走吧
Come on.
- 有子弹吗? - 没有
- Any bullets? - No.
- 而且是坏的 没法开枪. - 看
- It's broken, it won't fire. - Look.
这还能用
It works.
这好像是卫兵的制服
That's a piece of a guard uniform.
喔 让我们出去吧
Oh, let's get out of here.
走吧
Let's go.
怎么了?
What?
- 和我们那台一样的吗? - 喔 对!
- Is it the same one? - Oh, yeah!
- 能用吗? 你觉得能用吗? - 我看应该可以
- Will it work? Do you think it'll work? - I think so.
- 你他妈的没骗我吧? - 没问题 没问题 通知你弟吧
- Are you fucking kidding me? - Yeah, yeah, yeah. Call your bro.
嘿, 娜塔莉? 这里是保罗. 你们在吗?
Hey, Natalie? This is Paul. Are you guys there?
嗯,我们在 你们在哪?
Yeah, we're here. Where are you guys?
你一定不敢相信 我们找到了车子的电线
You're not gonna believe this. We got cables for the van.
你们哪时回来?
When are you coming back?
嗯 我们现在正往回走 我老弟现在如何?
Uh, we're heading back now. Uh, how's my brother doing?
他没事 你们快点回来
He's fine. Please hurry back.
因为我们很想快点离开这个该死的地方
'Cause we want to get the fuck out of here.
快走 快走!
Come on, come on!
嘿,克里斯? 你要撑住,兄弟 我们现在就回来!
Hey, Chris? You hang in there, buddy. We're coming back for you right now!
我们上路了
We're on our way.
快点, 柔依!
Come on, Zoe!
我跑不动了!
I can't run!
- 快! 快 快 快! - 喔 我的天!
- Go! Go, go, go! - Oh, my God!
走这边 这里 这里 这里!
This way. Here, here, here!
好, 快点, 快点!
All right, come on, come on!
快点!
Come on!
你可以的 宝贝
You're good, babe.
你一定能过! 你一定能过
You gotta go! You gotta go.
保持移动, 来!再来!
Keep moving, come on! Come on!
-你可以的! - 很好 很好
- You've gotta go! - All right, all right.
再来 再来
Come on, come on.
柔依,你得要继续移动 宝贝!
Zoe, you've gotta keep moving, babe!
- 柔依, 没问题的 - 再来, 柔依.
- Zoe, it's okay. - Come on, Zoe.
好!
Yes!
- 再来, 柔依! - 你做得到, 柔依!再来!
- Come on, Zoe! - You can do it, Zoe! Come on!
- 继续往前! - 柔依, 再来!
- Keep moving! - Zoe, come on!
喔 该死!
Oh, shit!
柔依!
'Zoe! 'Zoe!
- 好 这里 - 我拉到你了
- Good. Here. - Get back.
麦可!
Michael!
让他出来!
Get him out!
拉他上来
Get him up.
- 喔 我的腿!我的腿! - 你还好吗?
- Oh, my leg! My leg! - Are you okay?
- 一点点刮伤 这没事的 - 让他站起来 帮我让他站起来
- It's just a scratch. It's okay. - Get him up. Let's get him up.
拉我起来!
Pull me up!
- 走吧! - 我们得快走!
- Come on! - We gotta move!
- 看着我! 你没事吧? - 嗯 我没事
- Look at me! Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm okay.
大伙,走吧 我们他妈的快离开!
Guys, come on. Let's get the fuck out of here!
可恶!
Damn it!
腿怎么样?
How's the leg?
嗯, 我没事,伙计 我只想快点离开这里
Yeah, I'm all right, mate. I just want to get us out of here.
克里斯现在都应该到了莫斯科了
Chris should be in Moscow right now.
是啊, 但是他没有
Exactly, but he's not.
告诉我 你知道些什么 让我们弄清楚到底发生了什么
So tell me what you know so we can figure out what is going on.
我知道的只不过是都市传说
Just urban legend, man.
他们说这里并不是真的被废弃了
They say this place isn't really abandoned.
很明显的 辐射线并没有能够杀死一切
Well, obviously, the radiation hasn't killed everything.
- 我才不相信这些狗屁 - 为什么你不相信呢?
- I don't believe any of that shit. - Why not can't you believe it?
这里都已经废弃这么多年了...
There's so much that's been going on...
却还是要派卫兵拦路挡人
there's people gotta be out here doing this shit.
- 想想看! - 这里一定有着什么鬼东西 他是对的
- Think about it! - There has to be something. He's right.
- 我是说 想想吧 - 克里斯
- I mean, think about it. - Chris.
尤里 那东西把他弄到厨房里 那是要作什么?
Uri. That thing in the kitchen. What was that?
而且我发誓 我那天拍的照片里 有拍到甚么怪东西
And I swear there was something in a photo I took the other day.
我一开始没在意那是什么 但是...
I didn't think anything of it at the time, but...
- 你看? 有照片 - 那只是阴影吧...
- See? The photo. - It was a shadow...
如果甚么也没发生的话 那当然是不算甚么
It didn't make sense at the time, nothing had happened then.
听着 听着 ok?
Listen. Listen, okay?
- 柔依, 过来 - 走吧, 我们走!
- Zoe, come on. - Come on, let's go!
怎么了? 我们走错地方了吗
What? This is where we were.
- 他们把车发动了吗? - 而他们没通知我们?
- Did they get it started? - And they wouldn't call us?
- 娜塔莉? - 等等, 看! 在那里
- Natalie? - Wait, look! Over here.
什么? 那是车上的吗?
What? Is that from the van?
喔 我的天
Oh, my God.
搞什么鬼?
What the fuck?
哇 操 哇 操
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
克里斯!
Chris!
操!
Fuck!
-克里斯! - 哇!保持冷静 伙计
- Chris! - Whoa! Keep it down, mate.
嘿, 来这里!
Hey, come here!
-克里斯! - 嘿 伙计们！这有录影
- Chris! - Hey, guys! It's recording.
什么,什么?
What, what?
我不知道 这是克里斯.
I don't know. It's Chris.
-你说什么? -专心听
- What are you talking about? - Just listen.
-我爱你, 娜塔莉. - 我也爱你 宝贝
- I love you, Natalie. - I love you, too, baby.
- 我真的很爱你 - 我知道
- I love you so much. - I know.
我只是希望你知道
I just need you to know that.
我原本要等到莫斯科之后, 可是...
I was gonna wait 'til Moscow, but...
不 宝贝 等到了莫斯科再说
No, babe, wait till Moscow.
我们明天就在那里了...
We're gonna be there tomorrow...
然后你可以按原计画做好一切 ok?
and then you can do everything as planned, okay?
我知道, 但我只是...
I know, but I just...
那是什么?
What was that?
宝贝, 拿好相机 照那边看看
Babe, grab the camera. Shine it over here.
- 是他们回来了吗? - 我不知道
- Is that them? - I don't know.
- 你有看到什么吗? - 我没看到任何人
- Can you see anything? - I don't see anybody.
- 是保罗吗? - 我不知道
- Is it Paul? - I don't know.
- 到底发生了什么? 不... - 冷静点
- What the fuck is happening? No... - Keep it down.
-克里斯! -你得冷静下来和我们合作啊!
- Chris! - Keep your shit together!
冷静你妈的狗屁!
Stay the fuck away from me!
该死!保持冷静
Shit! Just keep it down.
- 我不会离开我弟弟的! - 他又不在这里
- I'm not leaving my brother! - He's not here.
-克里斯! -到底怎么了?
- Chris! - What was that?
-克里斯?克里斯?克里斯! -拜托 安静点
- Chris? Chris? Chris! - Please, be quiet.
操!
Shit!
克里斯!
Chris!
我们不该离开他们的  我们不该离开他们的  我们得找到他们
We can't leave them. We can't leave them. We need to find them.
我们得找到他们! 拜托!我们走吧!
We need to find them! Please! Let's go!
拜托, 麦可,我们得找到他们
Please, Michael, we need to find them.
- 该死的! - 拜托!
- Fucking hell! - Please!
那里 有经过那里
There, through there.
小心点
Careful.
喔,克里斯!
Oh, Chris!
娜塔莉?
Natalie?
克里斯?
Is that Chris?
Chris?
克里斯?!
Chris?!
过来, 柔依.
Come on, Zoe.
宝贝 我们得过去 他那里有枪 来吧
Baby, we have to, he's got the gun. Come on.
克里斯?!
Chris?!
娜?
Nat?
克里斯?!
Chris?!
- 他不在这 - 我听到他在 我听到他在
- He's not here. - I heard him. I heard him.
- 保罗! 我们得走了! - 我们不能留在这 我们走
- Paul! We've got to go! - We can't stay here. Let's go.
走吧 拜托? 拜托 伙计 我们会找到他的
Come on, please? Please, mate, we'll find him.
我很抱歉 走吧
I'm sorry. Come on.
!
RI-In!
娜塔莉!
Natalie!
来吧.来吧, 娜, 快来!
Come on. Come on, Nat, come on!
喔 天啊!
Oh, Jesus!
过来!走这里, 走这里!
Come on! This way, this way!
我扶着她! 我扶着她! Ok, 你没事了, 宝贝 你没事了
I got her! I got her! Okay, you're okay, baby. You're okay.
麦可?
Michael?
我找到你了 没事了 没事了
I got you. It's okay, it's okay.
这是他妈的地图 你看!
It's a fucking map. Look!
娜塔莉, 克里斯在哪?
Natalie, where's Chris?
娜塔莉,克里斯在哪?!
Natalie, where's Chris?!
保罗!
Paul!
我弟弟怎么了?
What happened to my brother?
我们往这边跑, 而他是不是在那里!
While we're going this way, he's in there!
嘿, 让她冷静一下!
Hey, leave her alone!
操
Shit.
娜塔莉,克里斯在哪里?
Natalie, where's Chris?
那些人...那些人抓住他
The people... They got him.
我们就在这条路上
That's the road we came in on.
然后我们就能到检查站 这边还有另一个检查点
So then we came onto the checkpoint, and that's another checkpoint.
现在我们在这里 嘿, 还有另一个检查哨!
And we're here. Hey, there's another checkpoint!
这很近的 我们可以到达那里找到帮手回来
It's close. We can get there. We'll find help and come back. I promise.
- 我现在不会离开 - 我懂, 可是我们必须去
- I can't leave yet. - I understand, but we got to go.
我不会丢下我弟弟的!
I'm not leaving without my brother!
我们一定要去!我们甚至不知道 克里斯是不是还...
We need to! We don't even know if Chris is still...
不准你他妈的这么说! 不准你他妈的这么说!
Don't you fucking say that! Don't you fucking say that!
把枪给我! 退后! 退后! 很抱歉, 伙计 我们想要帮你
Give me the gun! Back off! Back off! I'm sorry, mate. We want to help you.
我们会找到你弟弟的,我保证 但是我们必须去 我们需要协助
We'll find your brother, I promise, but we gotta go. We need help.
- 好吗? 好吗? - 保罗, 保罗?
- Please? Please? - Paul, Paul?
不, 保罗!
No, Paul!
我们得找到克里斯 可是如果连我们都死了 那他怎么办 对吗?
We're gonna find Chris but we are no good to him if we're dead, okay?
听我说! 听我说, 保罗, ok?
Listen to me! Listen to me, Paul, okay?
我们去群求帮助, 然后我们马上回来...
We're gonna go find help, and then we're gonna come back...
我们马上回来救你弟弟, ok?
and we're gonna get your brother, okay?
操 我们得离开这里 再给我看看地图
Fuck. We need to get out of here. Show me the map again.
现在, 我需要你跟我们一起行动
Right now, I need you to get it together.
这是为了其他人和我
For everyone else's sake and mine.
好吗?
All right?
走吧!
Come on!
这没有任何意义
That doesn't make sense.
辐射越来越强
The radiation's getting worse.
我们得继续走 快点! 我们得继续走 快点!
We've got to keep going. Come on. We've got to keep going, come on!
柔依,来吧
Zoe, come on.
- 这里, 麦可, 这说不通啊 - 你是什么意思?
- Here, Michael, it doesn't make sense. - What do you mean?
照地图的话，我们应该在这里?
Because the map says that we, we're supposed to be here?
- 我们得走那条路 - 不 但是你看
- We gotta go that way. - No, but look.
如果走这条路的话 应该会是...
It says that this way is supposed to be...
麦可, 看看这里, 那是死路!
Michael, look at it, it stops!
- 我们得往回走 - 我们到底该走哪里?
- Then we have to go back. - Which way do we have to go?
- 如果我们走回这里... - 我看不是这样 柔依, 柔依,拜托?
- If we go back here... - I know it's not. Zoe, Zoe, please?
- 麦可, 不对,我们得退回去! - 大伙 大伙!
- Michael, no, we have to go! - Guys, guys!
那是什么?
What the fuck?
等等!
Wait!
哈?
Hello?
你说什么?
What are you saying?
娜塔莉!
Natalie!
喔 我的天!
Oh, my God!
不!
No!
- 她到哪去了? - 她不见了!
- Where is she? - She's gone!
娜塔莉!
Natalie!
听着 听着 听着!
Listen, listen, listen!
这里 这里!
This way, this way!
柔依, 跟紧我
Zoe, stay in front of me.
该死的! 这是一个警卫!
Holy shit! That's a guard!
- 喔 我的天 - 走 走 走!
- Oh, my God. - Go, go, go!
娜塔莉?
Natalie?
娜塔莉?!
Natalie?!
-操! -继续走
- Shit! - We've got to go.
娜!
Nat!
- 她在哪? - 我不知道, 我不知道!
- Where is she? - I don't know, I don't know!
喔 操 喔 操
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
走 走 走! 快点!
Move, move, move! Come on!
麦可! 麦可!
Michael! Michael!
- 操, 太多了吧! - 快点!
- Fuck, there's too many! - Come on!
继续走, 继续走
Keep going, keep going.
这里 这边
Here, there.
他妈的快一点!
Hurry the fuck up!
快啊
Come on.
快!
Come on!
拉过来! 关上这该死的们!
Boxes! Shut the fucking door!
推!推!
Push! Push!
- 快点 快点 - 啊, 他们来了!
- Come on, come on. - Ah, they're coming!
- 踢它！ - 还有另外一个房间！
- Kick it! - There's another room back here!
麦可, 快点!
Michael, come on!
柔依,快点走! 走, 走, 走
Zoe, just get going! Go, go, 90
麦可!
Michael!
- 走 进去 进去! - 麦可!
- Go, get in, get in. - Michael!
柔依,快进去!
Zoe, get inside!
柔依, 快进去!
- 快! 把门关上 - 麦可!
- Come on! Close the door. - Michael!
- 推它!推它! - 卡住了!
- Push it! Push it! - It's stuck!
麦可, 快进来! 快进来!
Michael, get in! Get in!
麦可!
Michael!
他被困在那里！ 他逃不掉了！
He's trapped in there! He can't get out!
不,我们得进去
No, we have to go.
走!
Go!
柔依, 柔依, 柔依, 柔依.
Zoe, Zoe, Zoe, Zoe.
没事的 没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
- 不 不 不 不 柔依! -撑住, 柔依,来吧
- No, no, no, no, Zoe! - Get up, Zoe, come on.
我扶着你,我扶着你 来吧
I got you, I got you. Come on.
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
操
Shit.
别下去 别下去
Not down. Not down.
操!
Fuck!
走 走 走 走 走! 快!
Go, go, go, go, go! Go!
操!
Fuck!
哇操 把灯打开!
Oh, fuck. Put the light on!
柔依.
Zoe.
把他妈的灯打开!
Put the fucking lighten!
Put the fucking light on!
有人住在这里
This must be where they were living.
继续走 走吧 继续走
Keep moving. Come on, keep moving.
克里斯?克里斯?!
Chris? Chris?!
克里斯?
Chris?
走 走 走!
Go, go, go!
走哪边?
Which way?
来吧 我会帮你
Come on, I'll help you.
- 保罗,走! - 把手给我 来吧
- Paul, go! - Give me your hand. Come on.
- 喔 我的天! 他们来了! - 把手给我!
- Oh, my God! They're coming! - Give me your hand!
快 快!
Come on, come on!
不要! "快来!"
No! "Go!"
别放弃, 柔依!
Don't let go, Zoe!
不!
No!
不! 不!
No! No!
上来 上来
Up here, up here.
快 快 快!
Come on, come on, come on!
保罗?
Paul?
是我害了他们
I let them all go.
都是我的错
It's my fault.
别这样 别这样 我们会找到他们的
Come on, come on. We can still find them.
我们会找到他们的
We can still find them.
来吧,我们走 我们会找到他们 来吧
Come on, let's just go. We can still find them. Come on.
拜托? 拉着我的手 来吧
Please? Just take my hand. Come on.
我们得逃出这里
We gotta get outta here.
好像有什么跑进我眼睛
There's something wrong with my eyes.
操
Oh, fuck.
嘿, 我的脸好像被烧到一样
Hey, my face is burning.
靠 你看起来有点模糊
Fuck, you look all blurry.
怎么了?
What is that?
操! 操!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
快来!快来!拜托 快点!
Come on! Come on! Please, hurry!
-操! 什么都变模糊了 -我知道 Ok 抓着我
- Fuck! Everything's blurry. - I know. Okay, I got you.
我们得在辐射线杀了我们之前 找到路逃出去
We gotta find a way out of here before the radiation kills us.
- 你还好吗? -嗯,走吧 我还好
- Are you okay? - -Yeah, go. I'm fine.
小心 Ok
Careful. Okay.
喔 不
Oh, no.
我很遗憾 , 阿曼达.
I'm so sorry, Amanda.
不
No.
阿曼达, 我们不能待在这里
Amanda, we can't stay here.
我们不能待在这里 我们得继续走
We can't stay here. We have to go.
而且我没有你是走不了的, 所以拜托了,我们快走
And I can't leave without you, so please, let's just go.
- 等等 - 有出口
- Wait. - A way out.
操
Oh, fuck.
该死的
Holy shit.
不!
No!
跑! 快跑!
Run! Run!
我什么都看不到了
I can't see anything.
我看不...
I can't see...
救命!
Help!
- 救命! - 救命!
- Help! - Help!
救命!
Help!
- 谁来帮帮我们! - 救命!
- We need help! - Help!
拜托!
Please!
停住!不要再靠近!
Stop! Don't come any closer!
救救我们, 拜托!
Help us, please!
不要动!
S fop -!
-拜托 救救我们! -拜托,别这样!
- Please, help us! - Please, stop!
-不要! -拜托!
- No! - Please!
哈? 哈? 听得到我吗? 你叫什么名字?
Hello? Hello? Can you hear me? What is your name?
你要带我去哪里?
Where are you taking me?
喔 我的脸!
Ow, my face!
没事的 你是怎么进入皮里亚特的?
It's okay. How did you get into Pripyat?
那里面有人 他们在追我们
There were people. They were chasing us.
是的，病人，辐射尘的受害者 他们逃脱了
Yes, patients, victim of radiation. They escaped.
你看到他们了 是吗?
You saw them, yes?
他们杀了我的朋友
They killed my friends.
- 还有别人知道你去了那里吗? - 没有
- Anyone else know you're here? - No.
你要带我去哪里?
Where are you taking me?
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
我们在医院里 要带你去看医生
We're in the hospital. We're taking you to doctor.
逃脱的患者的状态如何?
What is the status of the patients that escaped?
全部都找到了
We got them all.
那些美国人呢?
And the Americans?
全都死了 除了这一个
All dead, except for this one.
- 你们在哪找到她? - 反应炉外面
- Where did you find her? - Outside the reactor.
我们不能让她走了
We can't let her go.
她看到他们了
She's seen them.
我的皮肤好像被烧伤了
My skin is burning.
你曝露在辐射线之下
You were inside reactor.
那可是非常危险的
It's extremely dangerous.
Ok...
Okay...
我们会帮忙的
We will help.
- 不 不 不! - 进去! 进去!
- No, no, no! - Go! Go!
谁在那里?
Who's there?